<idea-plugin version="2">
    <id>gr.jchrist.gitextender</id>
    <name>Git Extender</name>
    <version>0.3.0</version>
    <vendor email="io.christod@gmail.com" url="https://github.com/JChrist/gitextender">JChrist</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
        Git Extender adds an option to <em>Update All</em>
        local branches tracking a remote for all git roots in the current project<br/>
        Local branches that will be updated are the branches that exist locally and have been configured
        to track a remote branch.<br/>
        It fast-forwards commits in remote branches to local branches.
        If the local branch cannot be merged to the tracked remote using fast-forward only,
        then a simple merge will be attempted.
        If there are conflict errors, it will be aborted and an error notification will be shown.
        In this case, the update must be performed manually for the reported branch.<br/>
        After updating a branch, if there were any file changes, they will be displayed in
        IntelliJ Version Control tab.
        Currently, the correct list of file changes
        (updated, created, removed) will be displayed.
        However, when performing a diff for files in a branch other than the currently checked
        out, the diff will most probably be incorrect.<br/>
    ]]></description>

    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <ul>
            <li>
                0.3.0: Added configuration settings for GitExtender, offering options to control
                whether it will perform fast-forward-only merges, or if it will attempt simple merge and abort on error
                Also, instead of starting a thread for each module, it now uses an Executor with as many threads as there
                are available cores
            </li>
            <li>
                0.2.0: Keeping track of updated files, as results to be displayed after updating. ***Requires latest version: 145***
                The displayed updated files may show invalid/incorrect differences (in the show diff dialog)
            </li>
            <li>0.1.3: Changed pull method from rebase to merge, with the --ff-only flag (fast-forward only)</li>
            <li>0.1.2: Using GitFetcher to fetch and prune remotes and show results before starting the update</li>
            <li>0.1.1:
                Changed jdk to 1.7, so that the plugin works with IDEA running with 1.7 jdk
                Added check if any staged or unstaged changes exist in each repository, in order to stash only if needed</li>
            <li>0.1:
                Initial version of Git Extender, with support for updating all local branches tracking a remote of all git roots
in the current project, using rebase for all local commits and automatic stashing/popping of uncommitted changes</li>
        </ul>
    ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <!-- please see https://confluence.jetbrains.com/display/IDEADEV/Build+Number+Ranges for description -->
    <idea-version since-build="145"/>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.lang</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.vcs</depends>
    <depends>Git4Idea</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <!-- Add your extensions here -->
        <!-- Configuration state service ( persistable settings ) -->
        <applicationService serviceInterface="gr.jchrist.gitextender.configuration.GitExtenderSettings"
                            serviceImplementation="gr.jchrist.gitextender.configuration.GitExtenderSettings"/>

        <!-- provider for the configurable instance ( configuration settings ) -->
        <applicationConfigurable id="GitLabConfigurableProvider"
                                 provider="gr.jchrist.gitextender.configuration.SettingsConfigurableProvider"/>
        <projectService serviceInterface="gr.jchrist.gitextender.configuration.ProjectState"
                        serviceImplementation="gr.jchrist.gitextender.configuration.ProjectState"/>
    </extensions>

    <application-components>
        <!-- Add your application components here -->
    </application-components>

    <project-components>
        <!-- Add your project components here -->
    </project-components>

    <actions>
        <!-- Add your actions here -->
        <action id="GitExtender.UpdateAll" class="gr.jchrist.gitextender.GitExtenderUpdateAll"
                text="Git Extender -&gt; Update All"
                description="Update all locally tracked branches of all modules in the project">
            <add-to-group group-id="Git.Menu" anchor="first"/>
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="alt T"/>
        </action>
    </actions>

</idea-plugin>